Cinthya Castañeda

56 5396 2754 · contacto@casha.mx · Gustavo A. Madero, 07969, Ciudad de México, México

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

E-commerce professional with 7+ years of experience in the field of business with ability to deliver results. Some of my other skills include **Figma, UX, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and Google Analytics, Yoast**. Professional responsibilities include focusing on the **company's digital presence**, **enhancing the website's usability**, and pursuing **organizational objectives**.

KEY COMPETENCIES

Project ManagmentLeadershipProactiveEffective CommunicationFront End DevelopmentData AnalysisProblem SolvingCritical ThinkingDigital Marketing

WORK HISTORY

DoorDash, CA Feb. 2023 - Mar. 2024

Warehouse Associate

While being employed at DoorDash, I was involved in the task of determining the storage and products to be stocked based on the company's database. Below are the modifications that I made to ensure that the FIFO processes at the company were streamlined while at the same time guaranteeing the best stock for our clients.

GC Security Solutions, S.A. de C.V.

Jul. 2022 - Dec 2022

Asistente Adminsitrativa

At GC Security, I was among the key people who set its online foundation. Originally, they had a very low presence in the online space before I started working with them. After exploring the opportunities in WordPress, I designed and advanced their website and increased their interaction and inquiries by 5%. It greatly enhanced the user experience at the time and provided a solid framework for further digital advancements.

MKD Express Apr. 2021 - Jul 2022

Ecommerce Manager

In the current position of the Ecommerce Manager at MKD Express, I coordinated the improvement of the online presence on the platforms, including Mercado Libre and Amazon. I organized various significant events and set up a large fulfillment center within two weeks. Some of my responsibilities involved enhancing user experience on our ecommerce platforms to enhance customer s satisfaction and boost our KPIs.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

UX/UI Designer

CICC, 2024

Ingeníera en Sistemas Ambientales

IPN, 2015

Project Manager

Google, 2023

Ecommerce

ecommerce Institute, 2022

PROJECTS

Rediseño Sitioweb - GC Security Solutions

GC Security Solutions Mexico City, Mx.

Rediseño Sitioweb - Rainbowcafe

Rainbow Playground Cafe.

Vancouver, Ca.